James D. Kim

- Diamond Bar, CA CELL (909) 342-0400 E-MAIL bronze10000@gmail.com
- PORTFOLIO https://bronze10000.github.io/portfolio/

PROFILE

As a full-stack web developer with a background in research, I bring my love of learning and an analytical mindset honed from conducting experiments on a lab bench. My ultimate goal is to write awesome code as I continually improve my craft as a web developer.

EDUCATION

Web Development Immersive, General Assembly

1933 S. Broadway, Los Angeles, CA 90007 **B.S. in Botany,** University of California, Davis

1 Shields Ave, Davis, CA 95616

SKILLS Wordpress WooCommerce Shopify Liquid
Javascript JOuery CSS HTML

JavascriptJQueryCSSE-CommerceEbayAmazonBootstrapSEOGit

EXPERIENCE

Web developer at keepyourweddingdress.com

2020

- Create & modify company Wordpress website (Javascript, PHP, HTML, CSS)
- Search Engine Optimization of company web presence
- Convert to WooCommerce for e-commerce functionality
 - Utilize 3rd party plugins for logistics

Web developer at BNJ Abrasives

Nov., 2017 - 2019

- Create & modify company Wordpress website (Javascript, JQuery, PHP, HTML, CSS)
- Search Engine Optimization of company web presence
- Convert to WooCommerce for e-commerce functionality
 - Utilize 3rd party plugins for logistics
- Customer support

Contract web developer at The Joy Factory

Nov., 2016-Nov., 2017

- Modify company Shopify website (Liquid, Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS)
- Modify company microsite (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap)
- Search Engine Optimization of company web presence
- Integrate 3rd party apps with Shopify platform
- Use JQuery to create landing page animations
- Manage Ebay account (list products, customer service, handle company account)

Web developer at Pac Com International

Aug., 2016 - Nov., 2016

- Create & modify company Wordpress website (Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS)
- Search Engine Optimization of company web presence
- Integrate 3rd party apps with Wordpress platform
- Use JQuery to create landing page animations

Freelance web developer

since April, 2014

Develop Wordpress, WooCommerce, Zencart, Shopify websites

Researcher Spring, 2012- 2014

Studied role of Ecdysone Receptor in Aedes aegypti mosquito

REFERENCES Available upon request